http://www.expertlaw.com/terms-use-and-privacy-policy

Terms of Use
We believe ExpertLaw to be the best, largest, and most comprehensive free expert witness directory available online, and our directories of investigators and litigation support services continues to grow. This site is offered as a free service to the general public. Due to the nature of our service, all content provided by ExpertLaw is provided for use "as is". We provide no guaranties or warranties, express or implied, with regard to listings or content provided on this site.
The information provided on this site is provided by the experts and service providers themselves. We do not prescreen listed experts. We take no responsibility for the qualification, quality of work, or accuracy of representations made by the experts who are listed herein, and bear no responsibility for any disputes that may arise between any experts and their customers.
Although ExpertLaw may have modified or edited the submissions or parts thereof, or may have verified portions of the information provided, you use information provided by ExpertLaw at your own risk. ExpertLaw is not responsible for the accuracy or truthfulness of the information provided on this website, or on any website linked to or from ExpertLaw. We exercise no editorial control over the various websites linked by this service. It is the responsibility of the users of this service to independently investigate and verify the credentials of experts or services they choose to utilize, retain, or hire. the credentials of experts and services you choose to retain or utilize. ExpertLaw is not responsible for any losses, injuries or damages you may suffer, relating to the use of experts, consultants, investigators, or services contacted through this site.
Nothing on this website constitutes legal advice, and no attorney-client relationship, or other professional relationship, can be formed through the use of this website. Articles and information provided by ExpertLaw is for informational purposes only. Due to the nature of the law, it is possible that the information provided on ExpertLaw will not apply in your state or jurisdiction. Users rely upon any articles or information provided by ExpertLaw at their own risk. If you require legal assistance, please consult with a qualified attorney, licensed to practice in the jurisdiction where your legal needs have arisen. Please note that you should take legal advice only from a qualified, licensed attorney.
Forum Terms of Use
Registration to the forum is free. We do insist that you abide by the rules and policies detailed below. You agreed to these terms when you checked the 'I agree' checkbox and pressed the 'Register' button for the forum.
Although the administrators and moderators of the ExpertLaw Forum will attempt to keep all objectionable messages off this forum, it is impossible for us to review all messages. All messages express the views of the author, and neither the owners of the ExpertLaw Forum, nor Jelsoft Enterprises Ltd. (developers of vBulletin) will be held responsible for the content of any message. You hereby acknowledge that all posts made to these forums express the views and opinions of the author and not the administrators, moderators or webmaster (except for posts by these people) and hence will not be held liable.
You agree not to post any abusive, obscene, vulgar, slanderous, hateful, threatening, sexually-oriented or any other material that may violate any applicable laws. Doing so may lead to you being immediately and permanently banned (and your service provider being informed). The IP address of all posts is recorded to aid in enforcing these conditions. You agree that the webmaster, administrator and moderators of this forum have the right to remove, edit, move or close any topic at any time should they see fit. As a user you agree to any information you have entered above being stored in a database. Except as required by law this information will not be disclosed to any third party without your consent; however you agree that the webmaster, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised. Examples of when disclosure may be required by law include response to a subpoena or search warrant.
By posting content or making content available for inclusion on the ExpertLaw forums, including without limitation threads and comments you post to the forum, you grant ExpertLaw and its proprietors a world-wide, perpetual, irrevocable, royalty free, non-exclusive, fully sub-licensable license to use, distribute, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, publicly perform and publicly display, and to incorporate such content into other works in any format or medium now known or later developed.
This forum exists as a source of free information. You agree not to use this forum to endorse, promote or recommend any particular product or service, or any manufacturer, distributor, company or service provider. If somebody inquires about a particular product, service, manufacturer, distributor, company or service provider, you may provide factual information in response.
This forum system uses cookies to store information on your local computer. These cookies do not contain any of the information you have entered above; they serve only to improve your viewing pleasure. The e-mail address is used only for confirming your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one).
Information provided in this forum is not intended to substitute for informed legal advice, or other professional advice. If you submit a question or comment on such a topic, it is assumed that you are interested in soliciting and receiving or giving general information rather than professional advice. You should bear in mind that the applicability of such general information might vary substantially in different states and according to the individual factual circumstances surrounding a particular question or comment. Accordingly, if you desire or require legal or professional advice, please consult a lawyer or other qualified provider who is licensed in your state or country.
The questions or comments you submit and the responses you receive do not form the basis for a professional-client relationship, including but not limited to and attorney-client relationship, and are not subject to standards or requirements of confidentiality and/or privilege associated therewith.
This forum exists as a source of free information. You agree not to use this forum to endorse, promote or recommend any particular product or service, or any manufacturer, distributor, company or service provider. If somebody inquires about a particular product, service, manufacturer, distributor, company or service provider, you may provide factual information in response.
The owners of this forum reserve the right to remove, edit, move or close any thread for any reason.
By using these forums you agree to be bound by these conditions.
Privacy Policy
We respect our users' privacy, and take our users' privacy seriously. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. No user of this website needs to register an account or provide any information in order to browse this website as a visitor, and no user of this website is required to provide any personal information. While registered users gain access to additional features, and must disclose basic contact information for the purpose of confirming their accounts, it is up to individual users whether to provide any information beyond the amount required to complete the registration process.
We do not ask listed experts and services for information, feedback or statistics about users who contact or retain them.
The forum system and directory registration system use cookies to store information on your local computer. These cookies do not contain any of the information you have entered, and are meant to serve only to improve your viewing pleasure. The e-mail address you provide upon registration is used only for confirming your registration details and password (and for sending new passwords should you forget your current one), and occasional administrative or system messages. Examples of use of your personal information by this website include:
Upon Registration - When you register an account we will collect your chosen username, email address, and other information you opt to provide, and we will send an automatic email with information on how to complete the registration process.
Online Forms - If you submit an online form, the information you provide on that form may be used to respond to the form content or to contact you about your submission.
Automatic Messages - Our forum software automatically sends messages to users, including birthday messages for those who have entered a birth date. You may discontinue these messages with the settings feature found on your forum profile page.
Administrative Messages - You may receive an administrative message that relates to a problem encountered with the system, such as a data loss, or for registered professionals reminding you to verify the continuing accuracy of any information you have shared through articles, your profile, or directory listing.
Forum Content and Articles - if you put personal information in a forum post or article, that information will be publicly available. That information is not subject to our privacy policy, nor do we have any responsibility for any information you post in a public manner. You should be careful not to disclose any information that you do not want to be known to the public.
The IP address of all posted content is is recorded to aid in enforcing forum and website terms and conditions.
All users agree to any information they enter on this site, whether for registration as an expert, registration and use of the forums, or for any other purpose, being stored in a database. Except as required by law this information will not be intentionally disclosed to any third party without your consent; however you agree that the webmaster, administrator and moderators cannot be held responsible for any hacking attempt that may lead to the data being compromised. Examples of when disclosure may be required by law include response to a subpoena or search warrant.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
ExpertLaw is not responsible for the acts of third persons which may affect your privacy, including the conduct of advertisers on remotely hosted websites. When you view advertisements on the ExpertLaw website, third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information. You may adjust the settings on your browser to restrict who may place cookies on your computer, or to delete some or all of the cookies that are on your computer. We are not responsible for the conduct of websites linked to or from ExpertLaw.
Our website contains links to other websites, for the benefit of our users. Those websites are not under our control and are not subject to this privacy policy. We are not responsible for the content or privacy policy of other websites.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google. Google plants a cookie in your browser, and utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of this website, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. We use the information collected by Google Analytics to help improve this website and your user experience. The cookie placed by Google does not disclose any personal information about you to us, and cannot be used by anyone except Google. You may review the Google Analytics terms of service on Google's website.
Users may disable any cookies used by this website and continue to access the public content posted on this website. However, if cookies are disabled, the additional features we provide to registered users will not function properly. You may restrict or turn off cookies through your browser's privacy settings.
Your browser software may have a "do not track" feature to stop websites from tracking your movements. Due to the wide variety of browser software on the market, and our use of third party services, we cannot promise that your use of that type of feature will prevent your activity on this website from being tracked. However, the analytics software we use does not track activity by specific users or create a record of what material a specific user has accessed.
You may modify your personal information at any time by logging into your account and editing the information you previously shared with us.
In the event that this business merges or is acquired, in whole or in part, with another business, any personal information you have shared with this website may be transferred to the new business. Your personal information will remain covered by this privacy policy as it exists, or as it is amended by the new business.
This website is not intended for use by any person under the age of thirteen (13), and we do not intentionally collect any information from children. If you are a parent or guardian of a minor who you believe has attempted to register an account to access this website, please contact us. We may request proof of your identity prior to removing account information in order to prevent people from attempting to maliciously remove a registered user's account information.
We reserve the right to modify this policy at any time. However, this policy will remain in effect until a replacement policy is posted on this website. Registered users should receive a notice of any change in our privacy policies, either by email or by a message posted on this website or their profile page.
This privacy policy is limited to its express terms, and does not create any contractual or legal duty by ExpertLaw to any site visitor. This privacy policy applies only to users who use this website in accord with our "Terms of Use", and does not apply to protect the privacy of individuals who use this site in violation of those terms, or for illegal or abusive purposes.
Search form
Search
Legal Help, Information, and Resources
Legal ArticlesLegal articles on a wide range of subjects.
Expert Witness DirectoryEasy to use directory of expert witnesses.
Law Practice SupportProfessionals who provide support and consultation services to law firms.
Lawyer DirectoryDirectory of lawyers
Private InvestigatorsFind a private investigator.
Law ForumsDiscussion forums for legal questions and issues.
